<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>VEX.blue Articles</title>
    <link>https://vex.blue/article</link>
    <description>The lastest Articles hosted by VEX.blue</description>
    <category>News and Information</category>
    <copyright>2023 VEX.blue. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <enclosure url="https://vex.blue/assets/images/logos/vexitica" length="3000" type="image/png"></enclosure> 
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <!-- Posts (Newest to Oldest) -->
    <item>
      <title>Some Fediverse Software</title>
      <link>https://vex.blue/article/2024/09/15/fediverse-software</link>
      <description>The 'Decentralised Web' over time will grow into new applications and functions than the centralised counterparts, this is how the original web turned into forums and then further into Social Media, by taking something that already exists and expanding upon the idea of it...</description>
      <pubDate>2024-09-15 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Fediverse</category>
      <enclosure url="https://vex.blue/assets/images/thumbnails/article/2024-09-15-1.webp" length="74136" type="image/webp"></enclosure> 
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buses to Backpack</title>
      <link>https://vex.blue/article/2024/09/14/pillion</link>
      <description>I've spent the past month plus being a 'pillion' / passenger for someone on there motorbike, and I've got to say it far out beats getting the bus... So firstly what have I been doing on the back of a motorbike?</description>
      <pubDate>2024-09-14 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Motorbikes</category>
      <enclosure url="https://vex.blue/assets/images/thumbnails/article/2024-09-14-1.png" length="1114220" type="image/png"></enclosure> 
    </item>
    <!-- Please Update my Thumbnails & 'Length' -->
    <item>
      <title>Why we use RSS</title>
      <link>https://vex.blue/article/2024/09/13/why-we-use-rss</link>
      <description>So through our last 11 articles we've had at the bottom a RSS icon, This is so if you have a RSS reader (app or website) you will be able to follow our articles directly from the RSS...</description>
      <pubDate>2024-09-13 14:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Tech</category>
      <enclosure url="\assets/images/thumbnails/article/2024-09-13-1.png" length="78645" type="image/png"></enclosure> 
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I upgarded to an iPhone 15</title>
      <link>https://vex.blue/article/2024/09/12/iphone-15</link>
      <description>I've been an avid user of iPhone since the end of January this year, where I purchased my first iPhone, the iPhone SE Gen 2 (2020). When I got the phone it was for the pure reason to try out Apple, as upto that point I hadn't gave Apple an actual go other than a few times in the early days of iPads when...</description>
      <pubDate>2024-09-12 13:45:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Tech</category>
      <enclosure url="\assets/images/thumbnails/article/2024-09-12-1.png" length="78645" type="image/png"></enclosure> 
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Satisfactory 1.0</title>
      <link>https://vex.blue/article/2024/09/11/satisfactory-1.0</link>
      <description>Today Satisfactory 1.0 released, actually a lot sooner than what I thought it was going to (as I originally thought it was releasing at 8pm GMT). I stuck with my original plan and waited a few hours (as I had other things to do anyway) to play with 4 friends in a new world together...</description>
      <pubDate>2024-09-11 03:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Gaming</category>
      <enclosure url="\assets/images/thumbnails/article/2024-09-11-1.png" length="78645" type="image/png"></enclosure> 
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Light Mode is back</title>
      <link>https://vex.blue/article/2024/09/10/lightmode-is-back</link>
      <description>I know yesterday we announced Version 2.3 of the website but today we done even more work on making the website more accessible for everyone. Including bring back Lightmode...</description>
      <pubDate>2024-09-10 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>META</category>
      <enclosure url="\assets/images/thumbnails/article/2024-09-10-1.png" length="78645" type="image/png"></enclosure> 
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to Version 2.3</title>
      <link>https://vex.blue/article/2024/09/09/welcome-to-v2.3</link>
      <description>Welcome to Version 2.3 of the VEX.blue website, I recieved some feedback from very close friends about how the website was too bright and just seemed to have the feel of 'Apple'. This made me work with them closely to bring a new version of the website Version 2.3, this whole new Dark Theme is now the only way to view the website (currently) but in the future as I develop my skills I will learn how to intergrate a light theme as well into the site, I just want to make sure when you...</description>
      <pubDate>2024-09-09 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>META</category>
      <enclosure url="\assets/images/thumbnails/article/2024-09-09-1.png" length="78645" type="image/png"></enclosure> 
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Turn on Fediverse Sharing on Threads</title>
      <link>https://vex.blue/article/2024/09/08/fediverse-sharing</link>
      <description>Back when I wrote 'Decentralised Social Media' an article about the Fediverse and some of the various projects I mentioned about writing another article about how to turn on 'Fediverse Sharing' on threads. This is that article...</description>
      <pubDate>2024-09-08 16:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Fediverse</category>
      <enclosure url="\assets/images/thumbnails/article/2024-09-08--1.png" length="78645" type="image/png"></enclosure> 
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One Year of VEX.blue</title>
      <link>https://vex.blue/article/2024/09/07/one-year-of-vex.blue</link>
      <description>Yesterday marked our one year anniversary of becoming a company (September 6th, 2023 being our company registration date) and I can tell you we've made both lots of progress as well as so little in other areas, I took breaks from creating and pushing the company at times...</description>
      <pubDate>2024-09-07 13:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>META</category>
      <enclosure url="\assets/images/thumbnails/article/2024-09-07--1.png" length="78645" type="image/png"></enclosure> 
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Connect your Bluesky account to the Fediverse</title>
      <link>https://vex.blue/article/2024/09/06/connect-to-bluesky</link>
      <description>Having a Bluesky account can mean locking yourself off from the rest of the Fediverse at the moment, due to there custom protocol 'AT Protocol', I'm here today to give you a tutorial on how to make it so your Bluesky profile can be found on the rest...</description>
      <pubDate>2024-09-06 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Fediverse</category>
      <enclosure url="\assets/images/thumbnails/article/2024-09-06--1.png" length="78645" type="image/png"></enclosure> 
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'No Code' is bad</title>
      <link>https://vex.blue/article/2024/09/05/no-code-is-bad</link>
      <description>Have you ever wanted to build a website? Did you know how to 'code' that website? No, well there's sites like Wix, Wordpress and Square out there that allows you to just drag-and-drop your whole website or simply add plugins. These systems are plainly not terrible if you are making a dynamic website with logins and things, especially if you want to join...</description>
      <pubDate>2024-09-05 15:10:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Tech</category>
      <enclosure url="\assets/images/thumbnails/article/2024-09-05--1.png" length="78645" type="image/png"></enclosure> 
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retitling Blog to Articles</title>
      <link>https://vex.blue/article/2024/09/04/retitling-blog-to-articles</link>
      <description>A few days ago I started writing 'blog' posts for this website, starting with Welcome to v2.2 where I wrote about version 2.2 of the VEX.blue website. After creating my second post Decentralised Social Media, i'd started to realised that this 'blog' was much more than just me writing about the updates for this website and that I'd most likely want to write about the topics I love talking to people about (but they often don't understand).</description>
      <pubDate>2024-09-04 15:10:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>META</category>
      <enclosure url="\assets/images/thumbnails/article/2024-09-04--1.png" length="78645" type="image/png"></enclosure> 
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decentralised Social Media</title>
      <link>https://vex.blue/article/2024/09/03/decentralised-social-media</link>
      <description>Lately there's been plenty of talk about Threads, Bluesky, Mastodon and many more new Social Media platforms, along with something called the Fediverse. I thought I'd make a post about all of this, along with explain why we as VEX.blue actually love using these systems and encourage people to use them as well.</description>
      <pubDate>2024-09-03 00:20:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Fediverse</category>
      <enclosure url="\assets/images/thumbnails/article/2024-09-03--1.png" length="78645" type="image/png"></enclosure> 
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to Version 2.2</title>
      <link>https://vex.blue/article/2024/09/02/welcome-to-v2.2</link>
      <description>Welcome to version 2.2 of the VEX.blue website, I recently was looking across our wonderful website here and realised that it didn't look so great, possible due to me coding it myself from HTML, CSS and JS (what I don't know much about). So I spent the past few days working on making this website more simple and usable for the general user. This is not only handy for my learning of 'What makes a good website' but also now is getting to the point that I am learning more of what I can do with static websites like this one.</description>
      <pubDate>2024-09-02 18:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>META</category>
      <enclosure url="\assets/images/thumbnails/article/2024-09-2--1.png" length="78645" type="image/png"></enclosure> 
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>